(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T23:04:12.660705",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
輪堂千速生誕祭2026 Flat Out Summerte
Chihaya Rindou Birthday Celebration 2026: Flat Out Summerte
重大告知あり
Major Announcement Included
輪堂千速生誕祭2026、見に来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to Rindo Chihaya's Birthday Festival 2026!
盛り上がる準備できてるかー？
Are you ready to get fired up?!
ぶち上げていくぞー！
Let's kick it into high gear!
でもちょっと今から急いでライブ会場にみんなを連れて行かなきゃなんないから、
But I've got to rush and take everyone to the live venue right now...
一緒に行ってくれるか？行くぞ！
So will you come with me? Let's go!
熱くなった銀のメタリックハート
My silver heart is burning metal hot
導火線に火をつけてあげる
I'll light the fuse and watch it spark for you
不思議なほどハイな気分さ
Mysteriously feeling high today
砂埃を巻き上げて行こう
Let's kick the dust and leave it all behind
悲鳴をまじらせ暴走する鼓動
Mixing with the screams, my racing pulse goes wild
目の前にはミサイルの雨
Right before my eyes a rain of missiles falls
アドレナリンずっと流して
Keep adrenaline flowing through my veins
僕の方がオーバーヒートしそう
Feeling like I'm gonna overheat
爆発して灰になっても
Even if I burn and turn to ash
このままだと笑ってるね きっと
I'm sure I'll keep on laughing just like this
街を追い越して この世の果てまで
Pass the city lights to the end of the world
ぶっ飛ばして心中しよう さぁ手を伸ばして
Speeding to our death, come on reach out your hand!
地平線に届くように限界まで振り切ってくれ
Drive it to the horizon breaking through the line
Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
最高のフィナーレを Yeah!
Give me the best finale! Yeah!
もう数えるくらいで僕らは消え失せて
Countdown has begun till we fade to the dark...
真暗な朝が来るね
morning...
お気に入りの服に さぁ着がえたなら
Dress in your favorite clothes, now you're ready...
駆け出して!
just run out!
あきれるほど声を上げて
Shouting out so loud...
大気圏を突破しようぜ
till they've had enough of us!
Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
鋼の翼で
On wings of steel
駆けぬけてよ 時間切れまで
Race through till the end, till the time is running out
生まれつきのスピード狂なのさ
Born to be a speed freak, yeah, that's what I am
Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
来世でまた会おう Yeah!
See you in the next life, yeah!
広い宇宙の 数ある一つ
One of many in the vast universe,
青い地球の 広い世界で
in this wide world on the blue earth,
小さな恋の 思いは届く
the feelings of a small love will reach...
小さな島の あなたのもとへ
...to you on a small island.
あなたと出会い 時は流れる
Meeting you, time flows on...
思いを込めた 手紙もふえる
...and the letters filled with my feelings increase.
いつしか二人 互いに響く
Before we knew it, our echoes resonated together,
時に激しく 時に切なく
sometimes violently, sometimes painfully.
響くは遠く 遥か彼方へ
Echoing far away, to the distant horizon,
やさしい歌は 世界を変える
a gentle song changes the world.
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you,
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
the most precious person is right beside you.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
I just want you to receive this...
響け恋の歌
...echoing love song.
ほら...
Listen...
響け恋の歌
Echoing love song.
あなたは気づく 二人は歩く
You've realized, and the two of us walk.
暗い道でも 日々照らす月
Even in the dark, the moon shines on us daily.
握りしめた手 離すことなく
Holding hands tightly without letting go,
思いは強く 永遠誓う
this strong feeling vows for eternity.
永遠の淵 きっと僕は言う
At the edge of eternity, I'm sure I'll say
思い変わらず 同じ言葉を
the same words with unchanged feelings.
それでも足りず 涙にかわり
Even then it's not enough, turning into tears...
喜びになり
...and turning into joy,
言葉にできず ただ抱きしめる
unable to speak, I just hold you tight.
ただ抱きしめる
I just hold you tight.
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you,
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
the most precious person is right beside you.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
I just want you to receive this...
響け恋の歌
...echoing love song.
ほら...
Listen...
響け恋の歌
Echoing love song.
夢ならば覚めないで
If it's a dream, please don't wake me up.
あなたと過ごした時 永遠の星となる
The time spent with you becomes an eternal star.
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you,
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
the most precious person is right beside you.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
I just want you to receive this...
響け恋の歌
...echoing love song.
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you,
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
the most precious person is right beside you.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい
I just want you to receive this...
響け恋の歌
...echoing love song.
ほら...
Listen...
響け恋の歌
Echoing love song.
はーい！
All right!
というわけで、皆さん！輪堂千速生誕祭2026にお越しくださりありがとうございます！
And with that, everyone! Thank you so much for coming to Chihaya Rindou Birthday Festival 2026!
聴こえていますでしょうかー？
Can you all hear me out there?
挨拶します。
Let me introduce myself.
エキゾチックハイルネッツの、んっんっ、
Of Exotic High Lunettes...
やばい...
Oh boy...
ロックバンドのDJ兼運転手担当の輪堂千速です！こんちはー！
I'm Chihaya Rindou, DJ and driver of the rock band! Hello everyone!
ということで始まりました、初めての3D生誕ライブ！
And so, it has begun! My very first 3D birthday live concert!
いっぱい盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's get super hyped up together!
配信のハッシュタグは、右上...あっ、これ、これ、
The stream's hashtag is on the top right... Oh, wait, this one, this one,
右上のこちらになります。#輪堂千速生誕祭2026 になるので
It's this one right here on the top right. Since it's #RindouChihayaSeitansai2026,
たくさんポストしていただけるととっても嬉しいです。ちゃんと見ますからね！
I'd be so happy if you posted a lot with it. I'll definitely check them later!
ぜひあの、トレンド1位なんかになれたりしたら嬉しいななんて思うので、
I would be thrilled if we could reach trending number one, so please,
いっぱいスクショとかね、貼って、ポスト...
attach lots of screenshots and post them...
してもらえると 嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you did!
わぁ！ こんちはー！ ありがとう！
Wow! Hello! Thank you!
ということでね、一旦ちょっと2曲歌わせていただいたので
So, I've just sung two songs,
振り返っていこうかなと思うんですが
and I'd like to look back on them.
まずは1曲目、「Driver's High」を海沿いを
First, the first song, "Driver's High,"
フグタローでドライブしながら歌わせていただきました！
I sang it while driving along the coast in Fugutaro!
どうでしたでしょうか？
How was it?
デビューの一番最初に、L'Arc-en-Cielの曲を歌って
Right at my debut, I sang a song by L'Arc-en-Ciel,
この「Driver's High」を「いつか歌ってほしい」ってすごい一杯言われていたので
and I was often asked to sing "Driver's High" someday.
絶対に生誕で歌う！と思って、1曲目に選びました！
I decided to sing it at my birthday concert and chose it as the first song!
いや、あの、
Well, you see,
まあ、あの、あそこカバーの私有地なので
well, since that's Cover's private property,
色々諸々ひっくるめてオッケーです！大丈夫！
everything's perfectly fine! No worries!
大丈夫！きっと大丈夫！
It's fine! I'm sure it's fine!
そして、2曲目！「小さな恋のうた」でした！どうでしたか！？
And the second song was "Chiisana Koi no Uta"! How was it?!
そう！これ！
Yes! This!
千速が弾いていましたよー！
Chihaya was playing the guitar!
ご存知の方も多いかと思いますが、エレキを購入しまして練習していたんですが、
As many of you probably know, I bought an electric guitar and have been practicing.
弾かせていただきました！
I actually played it!
やっぱりなんかエレキで初めて挑戦するのって「小さな恋のうた」だよな、っていうイメージがあって
I always had this image that "Chiisana Koi no Uta" is the go-to first song to try on an electric guitar,
この曲を選んだんですけど
so I chose this song...
すっごい難しい！
But it was so hard!
すっごい難しかったんですけど、
It was incredibly difficult,
でも、生誕ライブでかっこいいところを見せたかったので
but I wanted to show my cool side at my birthday concert,
いっぱい、いっぱい、いっぱい練習して、
so I practiced over and over again,
弾けてたよね、なんとか。弾けてたと思います！
and somehow managed to play it. I think I did it!
なのでね、後でアーカイブとかも見直して、聴いてくれると嬉しいです！
So, I hope you'll rewatch the archives and listen to it again!
ということで、そしてね
And so, also,
お気づきの方もいますが、小さな恋のうた、最初は体育館だったんですけどサマーにできましたよー！
as some may have noticed, during "Chiisana Koi no Uta," we started in a gym,
外に出ることができましたよー！
but we managed to go outside!
やっぱ夏といえば外！海！山！自然！
Summer is all about the outdoors! The ocean! Mountains! Nature!
そして夏の音楽といえばフェス！をイメージして
And when you think of summer music, you think of festivals!
夏フェス会場になっております！
So we've made this into a summer festival venue!
後ろにはね、海もあって、最高のロケーションで
With the ocean behind us, it's the perfect location
今日はフェスを開催していければなと思っております！
to host our festival today!
こんなに広いのでね、あっちに行ったり、
Since it's so spacious, I can go over there,
あ、予定にない動きをしてすみません、本当に。
Ah, sorry for the unplanned movements, truly.
こっちに行ったりしていこうと思っています！
Or I can go over here!
では、ちょっとあんまり喋るとあれなので、次の曲いこうと思うので
Well, if I talk too much, we'll run out of time, so let's move on.
ちょっと準備するのでギターとマイク置いてきます！
I'll put away my guitar and mic to prepare.
ちょっと待っててね、行ってきます！
Just wait a bit, I'll be right back!
はい、ということで、はい！来ました来ました！
Alright, I'm back, I'm back!
ということで、ここからはですね、ゲストブロックになります！
So from here on, we're entering the guest block!
なので、この後もいっぱい楽しんでいってください！
I hope you'll continue to enjoy the show!
盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's get fired up!
We are Fighting Dreamers
高みを目指して
Aiming high!
Fighting Dreamers
なりふり構わず
Not caring about appearances,
Fighting Dreamers
信じるがままに
Just as we believe,
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Let it go like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
Slash through it and get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Let it go like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
険しい修羅の道の中
Along this steep and treacherous path,
他人(ひと)の地図を広げて何処へ行く?
where are you going, following someone else's map?
We are Fighting Dreamers
高みを目指して
Aiming high!
Fighting Dreamers
なりふり構わず
Not caring about appearances,
Fighting Dreamers
信じるがままに
Just as we believe,
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Let it go like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
信じるがままに
Just as we believe,
Oli Oli Oli Oh- Just go my way!
One, two, right now!
(Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー
(Bang!) Fire it off like a bullet!
Right here, Right now!
(Bang!) ぶった斬ってくぜ Get on fire!
(Bang!) Cut it down, get on fire!
One, two, right now!
(Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー
(Bang!) Fire it off like a bullet!
Right here, Right now!
(Bang!) ぶった斬ってくぜ Get on fire!
(Bang!) Cut it down, get on fire!
We are Fighting Dreamers
この仲間達と
with these comrades,
Fighting Dreamers
すべてを巻き込み
dragging everything in,
Fighting Dreamers
志高く
with our ambitions high!
Oli Oli Oli Oh- Just go my way!
We are Fighting Dreamers
高みを目指して
aiming for the heights,
Fighting Dreamers
なりふり構わず
regardless of how we look,
Fighting Dreamers
信じるがままに
just as we believe,
Oli Oli Oli Oh- Just go my way!
Go my way!
Don't forget your first impulse
Keep your adventure, let's start!
Go my way!
Don't forget your first impulse
Keep your adventure, let's start!
One, two, right now!
(Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー
(Bang!) Fire it off like a bullet!
Right here, Right now!
(Bang!) ぶった斬ってくぜ Get on fire!
(Bang!) Cut it down, get on fire!
One, two, right now!
(Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー
(Bang!) Fire it off like a bullet!
Right here, Right now!
(Bang!) ぶった斬ってくぜ Get on fire!
(Bang!) Cut it down, get on fire!
Bang!
ガラス玉ひとつ 落とされた
A single glass ball fell.
追いかけてもうひとつ落っこちた
When I went after it, I dropped another one.
ひとつ分の陽だまりに
There's only enough sun for one,
ひとつだけ残ってる
and only one is left.
心臓が始まった時
As soon as your heart starts beating,
嫌でも人は場所を取る
you take up space, whether you want to or not.
奪われない様に
To prevent it from being stolen,
守り続けてる
you keep protecting it.
汚さずに保ってきた手でも
Even with hands kept clean,
汚れて見えた
they now look dirty.
記憶を疑う前に
Before I can doubt my memories,
記憶に疑われてる
my memories are doubting me.
必ず僕らは出会うだろう
We will meet for sure,
同じ鼓動の音を目印にして
using our heartbeats as signs.
ここに居るよ
I am here,
いつだって呼んでるから
always calling for you,
くたびれた理由が 重なって揺れる時
when the tired old reasons pile up and start to sway,
生まれた意味を知る
that's when you know the reason you were born.
存在が 続く限り 仕方無いから 場所を取る
As long as life exists, we take up space whether we want to or not.
ひとつ分の陽だまりに ふたつは ちょっと入れない
Two can't fit when there's just enough sun for one.
ガラス玉ひとつ 落とされた
A single glass ball fell.
落ちた時 何か弾き出した
And when it did, something shot out.
奪い取った場所で 光を浴びた
It bathed in the light in the spot it stole.
数えた足跡など
Counting my footprints,
気付けば数字でしかない
but at some point it became just a number.
知らなきゃいけない物は
Apparently what I mustn't know
どうやら1と0の間
is between one and zero.
初めて 僕らは出会うだろう
We will meet for the first time,
同じ悲鳴の旗を目印にして
using our screaming flags as signs.
忘れないで いつだって呼んでるから
Don't forget, I'm always calling you,
重ねた理由を 二人で埋める時
when we bury all the piled-up reasons,
約束が交わされる
that's when we'll make a promise.
鏡なんだ 僕ら互いに
We are mirrors, both of us,
それぞれのカルマを 映す為の
reflecting each other's karma.
汚れた手と手で 触れ合って
Our dirty hands will touch,
形が解る
and we'll know its shape.
ここに居るよ
I am here,
確実に触れるよ
and I can touch you.
一人分の陽だまりに 僕らは居る
In this sun that's only enough for one, we are both here.
忘れないで いつだって呼んでるから
Don't forget, I'm always calling you,
同じガラス玉の内側の方から
from the inside of the same glass ball.
そうさ 必ず
Yeah, we will surely
僕らは出会うだろう
meet again.
沈めた理由に 十字架を立てる時
When you build a cross on the sunken reasons,
約束は果たされる
the promise will be fulfilled.
僕らはひとつになる
We will become one.
今日も君は
Today too, without forgetting...
信じること
...to believe...
忘れずに目覚められていますか？
...are you awake?
時が経つと
As time passes,
自分さえも
even your belief in yourself...
信じられなくなる時代のようです
...fades in this kind of era.
自分では気付かないのが
Not noticing it yourself
この症状の特徴で
is the characteristic of this symptom.
唯一ある予防法...は
The only prevention method is...
「自分に嘘だけはつかない事」
...to not lie to yourself.
忘れてたまるもんかよ！！
How could I ever forget that?!
僕がボクじゃなくなったら
If I stop being myself,
たとえ生きてたって
even if I were alive,
生きてる意味すら見つからんだろ
I wouldn't even find a reason to live!
声にならない叫びは
The shout that can't become a voice,
僕が声を枯らして
I'll wither my voice,
叫んで歌って
screaming and singing,
伝わるまでわめいて
shouting until it reaches you,
届くまで止めない！！
and I won't stop until it does!
今日も地球は
Even today, the Earth...
回り続ける
...keeps spinning.
誰が泣いても怒っても止まらず
Never stopping no matter who cries or gets angry.
ためしに僕が...
Even if, for example, I...
風邪をひいても
...were to catch a cold,
もちろん止まる事なんてねーわ！！
of course, there's no way it would stop!!
人生も同じように
Life is just the same,
止まる事はなく進むし
it moves forward without ever stopping.
だからそうさ今日も人は
So indeed, today too, people...
お手手のシワとシワをあわせんの
...join their hands together!
終わらせちまう事なんか
Giving up on things,
誰にだってできんだろ？！
anyone can do that, right?!
たとえ終わっちまったって
Even if it has come to an end,
次のスタートすぐきれんだろ？！
you can start over right away, right?!
今キミが思うキセキも
Even the miracle you're thinking of right now,
底上げさせてしまえば
if you just raise its standards,
もうその時点でそのキセキは
then at that very moment, that miracle...
君にとっちゃ必然のお仲間さ！！
...will inevitably become your friend!
WOW!!
何回ダメダメと言われようが
No matter how many times they say it's no good,
実際問題そんなん関係なくて
practically speaking, that doesn't matter.
今、自分自身必要なものたくわえて
Right now, gather what you yourself need...
そろえとけよ！！
...and have it ready!!
なぁそうだろ？！
Isn't that right?!
まだまだ！！ 時間はまだあんぞ！！
Not yet, not yet!! There's still time!!
先見の明 今はとぎすまして
Sharpen your foresight now.
主人公は一人だけ！！
There's only one protagonist!!
自分の物語のはじまり！！
It's the start of your own story!!
もうすぐ時計は6時
Soon the clock will strike six.
もうそこに一番星
The first star is already there.
影を踏んで夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
On my way home, I want to step on shadows
and disappear into the night.
どんなに探してみても
No matter how hard I search,
一つしかない星
there's only one star.
…億光年 離れたところから
...from billions of light years away,
あんなに輝く
shining so bright.
いいな 君は
How nice, you are...
みんなから愛されて
...loved by everyone.
いいや 僕は
\"No, I am...
ずっと一人きりさ
...always all alone.\"
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
星降る夜 一瞬の願い事
a fleeting wish on a starry night.
きらめいて ゆらめいて
Sparkling, flickering...
震えてるシグナル
...trembling signals.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
空見上げて 指を差されるような
as if being pointed at when looking up at the sky.
つないだ線 解かないて
Please don't unravel the lines we connected,
僕がどんなに眩しくても
no matter how dazzling I might be.
もうすぐ時計は8時
The clock is almost at 8,
夜空に満天の星
with a night sky full of stars.
何億光年 離れたところには
Billions of light years away,
もうないかもしれない
they might not even exist anymore.
月が綺麗で 泣きそうになるのは
The moon is so beautiful it makes me want to cry,
いつの日にか 別れが来るから
because one day, a parting will come.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
彗星みたい 流れるひとりごと
flowing monologues like comets...
消えていく残像は
The fading afterimages...
真夜中のプリズム
...are a midnight prism.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
切なる願い 誰かに届いたら
if my earnest wish could reach someone.
変われるかな 夜の淵を
Could I change, as I trace...
なぞるような こんな僕でも
...the edge of the night, even as I am?
遥か彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった
Far, far away, we have crossed paths.
カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまうよ
It must be karma, for we will keep meeting again and again...
雲の隙間で
...in the gaps between the clouds.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
夜広げて 描こう絵空事
let's spread the night and paint our fantasies,
暗闇を照らすような 満月じゃなくても保存
even if we aren't a full moon illuminating the darkness.
だから集まって星座になりたい
That's why I want to gather and become a constellation,
色とりどりの光 放つような保存
emitting multicolored lights.
つないだ線 解かないよ
I won't let go of the lines we connected,
君がどんなに眩しくても
no matter how dazzling you might be.
はい！ということで！FGちゃーん！
Alright! And with that... Flow Glow!
イェーイ！
Yay!
聞いてくれてありがとうございました！ありがとー！
Thank you so much for listening! Thank you!
はー、しんどい。大丈夫？
Phew, I'm exhausted. Are you guys okay?
歌うことですね。一息整えてね、大丈夫？
Because of all the singing! Let's catch our breath. You okay?
あの、FGでね、ずっとバンドがやりたいと思っていたので
You know, we've always wanted to play as a band in FG...
ま、今日はエアバンドなんですけれども、みんなで「星座になれたら」披露させていただきました！
...so though it's just an air band today, we got to perform "Seiza ni Naretara" together!
楽しかったー！ありがとー！
That was so much fun! Thank you!
一回自己紹介しとくか。オッケー！じゃあ、りっちゃから！
Shall we do a quick round of self-introductions? Okay! Let's start with Riccha!
いつもの自己紹介で、お願いします！
Give us your usual intro, please!
はーい！私の歌に合図を！リオナ・エンドハース！
Hi! Signal to my song! Riona Endhearth!
Flow Glowの、ベース担当、リオナです！
Flow Glow's bassist, Riona!
低い声かっこいいよ、リオナ。ちーちゃん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Your low voice is so cool, Riona! Chi-chan, happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そして！ニコたんが来たー！Flow Glowの、キーボード担当、ニコたんだよ！
And next! Nikotan is here! Flow Glow's keyboardist, Nikotan!
ニコたん、ありがとう！ありがとうー！
Nikotan, thank you! Thank you!
そして！はーい！ピチピチの、お祝いするために来ました！
And next! Hi! I came here fresh to celebrate!
Flow Glowの、ドラム担当、すうです！
Flow Glow's drummer, Su!
ちーちゃん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Chi-chan, happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そして！あ、はい！
And... Oh, yes!
せーの、びび！
One, two, Vivi!
いつもはキラキラな、キラキラビビです！
I'm the usually sparkling, Kira-Kira Bibi!
あ、忘れてた。ビビはギター担当！ドルルルル...
Oh, I forgot. Bibi is on guitar! *guitar sounds*
ちーはー、お誕生日おめでとう！
Chihaya, happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いや、ということで、みんな来てくれてありがとう！
Anyway, thank you all for coming!
ありがとう、え、なんかいいおしらせがあるんじゃないの？
Thank you! Wait, don't you have some good news?
なんと！トレンド1位になったらしい！
Unbelievably, we trended #1!
やったー！
Yay!
なんか、今までね、ちはやって2文字だからトレンドに乗らねえのよ。
You see, "Chihaya" is only two characters, so it usually doesn't trend.
あー、なるほどね、なるほどね。
Ah, I see. That makes sense.
だから、乗ったらいいなと思ってたんだけど、こんな誕生日に嬉しいプレゼントいただきまして本当にありがとうございました。
So I was hoping it would, and getting such a wonderful birthday present makes me so grateful.
いっぱいツイートしてくれた、ありがとう！
Thank you everyone for tweeting so much!
もっとしってね、もっとしってね。
Keep it going! Keep tweeting!
はい、ということで、生バンド、いかがでしたでしょうか。
Yes! So, how was our live band performance?
楽しかった！
It was so much fun!
ドラムも叩きたくなりました。
It made me want to play the drums too.
叩いてたもんね、ドラムね。
You were totally playing the drums, weren't you?
経験者なんだよね、実はそうなんです。
You've played before, right? Actually, yes, I have.
だから、いつかFGバンドをね...
So, one day, we should form an FG band...
絶対にできる、できる！結成したい！
We can definitely do it! I want to form one!
今回はエアバンドだったので、ニコたんにキーボードを担当していただいたんですけど。
Since it was an air band this time, we had Nico-tan play the keyboard.
ねえ、すごかったでしょ？
Hey, I was pretty great, wasn't I?
すごかった、本当にすごかった！
You were amazing, truly amazing!
手で弾いてたもんね。全然弾いてくれてた。
You were playing with your hands. You were really getting into it.
そういうことやね。
Exactly.
一歩も触れずにね。
Without touching it even once.
でも、めっちゃみんな楽し、ちーもすごい楽しかったし、
But it was so much fun! I had a blast,
なんかも楽しそうにしてくれてとっても嬉しかったです。
and I'm so happy everyone else enjoyed it too.
いつか実現させましょう！やりたいやりたい！やりたい！
Let's make it happen someday! I want to, I want to!
そんな時はみんな今回の楽器でいいんですか？
When we do, are you all okay with the same instruments?
あ、え、え、あれ？
Oh, wait...
別の楽器がやりたい！歌、歌う！
I want a different instrument! I'll sing!
歌うのはダメ！ダメダメ！
No singing! No way!
ニコたんはさ、やるとしたら何の楽器やりたい？
Nico-tan, what instrument would you want to play?
え、だって、何でもいいよ。もう出まくってるよね、もう。
I mean, anything is fine. I'm already out of options.
ギター？今、ギター、ギター、ドラム、ベースがいるんだけど、そしたらでもやっぱキーボードしかない。
Guitar? Currently we have guitar, drums, and bass. So keyboard is the only option left.
でも、バイオリンがあるやん。
But there's always the violin.
バイオリン？ちょっと違う気がする。
Violin? I feel like that doesn't fit.
打楽器がどう？トライアングルとか。
How about percussion? Like a triangle.
ビビはトライアングル、ビビはトライアングル。
Bibi on the triangle, Bibi on the triangle.
ビビもトライアングル、いいかも。
Bibi on the triangle might be good too.
全員でなんか打楽器バンド！
Let's all just be a percussion band!
打楽器バンド！それいいかも！
A percussion band! That sounds nice!
それ全然違う打楽器。やめろそれ。違う、違う。
That's a completely different kind of percussion! Stop that!
そういうのもやってみたい、楽しそう。
I'd love to try something like that, it sounds fun.
FGの企画とかでやったりするのね。
Maybe we could do it as an FG special project.
確かに。やろうやろう。やりましょう。
True! Let's do it, let's do it!
ということでね、今回はFGちゃんたちに来ていただきまして、本当に今日はね、長い時間リハーサルから付き合ってもらって、本当にありがとう！
So, thank you so much to the FG members for joining us today, and for staying with us for so long since rehearsals!
おめでとう！ありがとう！
Congratulations! Thank you!
千速がなんでもします券を皆様に贈呈いたします。
I hereby present you all with a "Chihaya will do anything" voucher.
え！何でもって言ったの！？何でもいいの！？
What?! Did you say "anything"?! Anything goes?!
お一人一枚？お一人一枚、やったー！
One for each of us? One for each, yay!
うわ、どうしよう、取り消し！取り消し！取り消し券なし！
Wait, what should I do? Cancel! No cancellation voucher!
美味しいご飯ごちそうさまです。
You're treating us to a delicious meal!
それはもちろん全員に奢らせていただきます。
Of course, I'll happily treat all of you.
よかった、よかった。乗せてください。
Awesome! Treat us well!
今日も、お弁当豪華だった。お弁当、奮発しました。
Today's bento was really fancy too. I splurged on them!
よかった喜んでいただいて。
I'm glad you liked them.
ありがとう。まだあるので持って帰ってください。はい！...
Thank you! There's still some left, so feel free to take them home. Yes!
ではね、そろそろ次の曲に行きたいと思います！...
Well then, it's about time we move on to the next song!
みんなも見ててくれるかな？
Will you all keep watching?
バッチリ！
Absolutely!
では、ライブ見てくれている皆さんも、まだまだ盛り上がって行ってくださいね！
To everyone watching the live stream, keep pumping up the excitement!
イェーイ！
Yay!
まだコメント欄は何でもって言っている。
The comment section is still repeating "anything".
リスナーさん達には何もしないですけど、FGちゃん達には何でもしたい気持ちでいますよ。
I won't do "anything" for the listeners, but I'm ready to do anything for the FG members.
すぐ帰ろうとしないで。
Hey, don't try to leave so quickly.
もちろんそれぐらいの愛があります。気持ちだけじゃなくてね。
Of course, I have that much love for you all. Not just in spirit, okay?
おねがいします。やばいやばい。
We're counting on you! Oh dear.
みんな、バイバイ！ありがとうね！...
Bye-bye, everyone! Thank you so much!
俺も一緒に行こう。シュシュシュシュ...
Let me tag along too. *sfx: whoosh*
あの日見渡した渚を
I can still remember the shore we saw that day...
今も思い出すんだ
I still remember it even now...
砂の上に刻んだ言葉
The words we wrote in the sand...
君の後ろ姿
The sight of you as you turned away...
寄り返す波が
The waves ebb and flow
足元をよぎり何かをさらう
across my feet, carrying something away
夕凪の中 日暮れだけが
In the evening calm, twilight alone
通り過ぎてゆく
passes me by
パッと光って咲いた
We watched fireworks blooming
花火を見てた
in a flash of light
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely this summer is far from over
曖昧な心を
And has unraveled our uncertain hearts,
解かして繋いだ
tying them together
この夜が続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to go on forever
あと何度君と同じ花火を
I wonder how many times I'll be able to watch the same fireworks as you
見られるかなって
with you...
笑う顔に何ができるだろうか
What can I do for the sake of your smiling face?
傷つくこと 喜ぶこと
Feeling hurt, feeling happy...
繰り返す波と情動 焦燥
Repetitive waves and emotions, frustration...
最終列車の音
and the sound of the evening's last train
何度でも言葉にして君を呼ぶよ
Again and again, I'll put it into words, and call to you
波間を選び もう一度
Seeking the pause between waves, I'll try once again...
もう二度と悲しまずに済むように
So that you'll never have to feel sad again
ハッと息を呑めば 消えちゃいそうな光が
A light that seemed it might disappear if we let out a gasp
きっとまだ胸に住んでいた
Surely remained within our hearts
手を伸ばせば触れた
When we reached out our hands, we touched...
温かい未来は
the warm future
ひそかに二人を見ていた
that was secretly watching us
パッと花火が
Fireworks, in a flash of light
夜に咲いた
Bloomed in the night
夜に咲いて
静かに消えた
And disappeared silently
離さないで
Don't let go
離れないで
Don't go away
もう少しだけ
Just a little longer
もう少しだけこのままで
Let us stay like this just a little longer
あの日見わたした渚を
I can still remember the shore we saw that day...
今も思い出すんだ
I can still remember it now...
砂の上に刻んだ言葉
The words we wrote in the sand...
君の後ろ姿
The sight of you as you turned away
パッと光って咲いた
We watched fireworks blooming
花火を見てた
in a flash of light
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely this summer is far from over
曖昧な心を
And has unraveled our uncertain hearts,
解かして繋いだ
tying them together
この夜が続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to go on forever
ららら...
La la la...
思い違いは空のかなた
Mistaken thoughts from beyond the sky
さよならだけの人生か
Is it a life spent saying goodbye?
ほんの少しの未来は見えたのに
Even though I saw a tiny glimpse of the future...
...えたのに
...even though I saw...
さよならなんだ
it was goodbye.
昔住んでた小さな部屋は
The small room I once lived in...
今は誰かが住んでんだ
...is now occupied by someone else.
君に言われたひどい言葉も
Even the harsh words you said to me,
無駄な気がした毎日も
and the days that felt wasted...
あの時こうしてれば
If I had done this back then,
あの日に戻れれば
if I could go back to that day...
あの頃の僕にはもう戻れないよ
I can't return to the way I was back then anymore.
たとえばゆるい幸せが
Say, if a gentle happiness...
だらっと続いたとする
...were to drag on lazily...
きっと悪い種が芽を出して
A bad seed would surely sprout...
もうさよならなんだ
...and it'd be goodbye once more.
寒い冬の冷えた缶コーヒー
A cold canned coffee in the freezing winter,
虹色の長いマフラー
and a long, rainbow-colored scarf.
小走りで路地裏を抜けて
Running through the back alleys,
思い出してみる
I try to remember.
たとえばゆるい幸せが
Say, if a gentle happiness...
だらっと続いたとする
...were to drag on lazily...
きっと悪い種が芽を出して
A bad seed would surely sprout...
もうさよならなんだ
...and it'd be goodbye once more.
なんだ
Goodbye...
さよなら それもいいさ
Goodbye, that's fine too.
どこかで元気でやれよ
Be well out there somewhere.
さよなら 僕もどうにかやるさ
Goodbye, I'll manage somehow too.
さよなら そうするよ
Goodbye, that's what I'll do.
はい、はい！
Okay. Okay!
はい、ということで「ソラニン」をお送りいたしました。いかがだったでしょうか？
Yes, so I just performed "Soranin". How did you like it?
いや、あの、見覚えがある方もいらっしゃるのではない…でしょうか？
Well, some of you might find this familiar, right?
これ、まあ初めて見る方もいらっしゃるかなと思うんですが、
Though I'm sure some of you are seeing this for the first time,
あの、FGの3Dお披露目の時にも、えっとギターの弾き語りをお披露目させていただいたんですけれども、
I actually played an acoustic guitar cover during FG's 3D debut stream as well,
その時よりもレベルアップできていたでしょうか？
do you think I've improved since then?
初めて多分最初の頃に練習したのがソラニンで、そこからずっとちゃんとできた姿をみんなに見せたかったのでこの曲を選びました。
Probably the first song I ever practiced was "Soranin", and since then, I've always wanted to show everyone a properly polished performance, which is why I chose this song.
そしてですね、ギター、千速の音だけじゃなくて、もう一本、ソロとかベースがあったと思うんですが、
And also, as for the guitars, you probably noticed there wasn't just my sound, but also a solo guitar and a bass,
それはですね、千速のギターの先生に一緒に弾いていただきました！
those were actually played together with my guitar teacher!
なんかレッスンの時に、セッションしてたら「え、めっちゃかっこよくね？」ってなって、「先生もよかったら一緒に弾いてくれませんか？」って言って、一緒にね、弾いていただきました。ありがとうございました！
During one of our lessons, we were jamming together and we were like, "Whoa, isn't this super cool?" So I asked, "Teacher, would you like to play along with me?" and we ended up playing it together. Thank you so much!
ということでね、一旦ここまでの振り返りをして行こうかなと思いますよ。
So, I think I'll take a moment to look back on what we've done so far.
まずはゲストパートで、一曲目が...
First off, in the guest segment, the first song was...
ツバハチでGo! Fighting Dreamersしました。どうですか？
Let's go with Tsubahachi! We sang "Fighting Dreamers." How was it?
やっぱり1曲目はぶち上げていきたいなと思って、ツバハチでね、めっちゃ盛り上がる曲を選びました。
I really wanted to start off with a bang for the first song, so I chose a super hype song with Tsubahachi.
もう先輩たちのぶち上げがカッコよくて、ちーちゃんも頑張るぞーってなったので、楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
Seeing the seniors hype things up was so cool, it made me go, "I'll do my best too!" I hope you enjoyed it.
そして2曲目は、トワ様とカルマを歌いました。
And for the second song, I sang "Karma" with Towa-sama!
やっぱりトワ様の低音が大好きなので、ちょっと無理を言って原曲キーでね、すごい低い中、一緒に歌っていただきました。トワ様、ありがとうございました！めっちゃカッコよかったです！
I absolutely love Towa-sama's low range, so I asked to sing in the original key, and we sang together in that very low register! Thank you, Towa-sama! It was so cool!
そして3曲目が、ルイ先輩と「自分ROCK」！いや、カッコよすぎない？やっぱりルイ先輩カッコよすぎない？ヤバいんですけど。
And the third song was "Jibun ROCK" with Lui-senpai! I mean, isn't that just too cool? Right? Lui-senpai is just too cool, it's crazy!
あの本当にルイ先輩の、カッコいい、ちょっとこうがなりの効いた、エッジの効いた声で歌いたいなと思ってこの曲を選びました。超カッコよかったよね！
I really wanted to sing this song with Lui-senpai's cool, slightly raspy, edgy voice, so I chose it. It was incredibly cool, wasn't it?
そして6曲目が「星座になれたら」。さっきね、フブちゃんたちと一緒にワイワイした「星座になれたら」で、
And the sixth song was "Seiza ni Naretara"! We had so much fun singing it with Fubu-chan and the others just a moment ago.
7曲目、激エモな、にゃんちゃん、おかゆ先輩との「打上花火」、どうでしたか？もうマジで、あの本当に、
The 7th song was a super emotional "Uchiage Hanabi" with Nyan-chan and Okayu-senpai! How was it? Honestly,
おにぎり、あの皆さんには申し訳ないんですけれども、あの瞬間はちょっと自分、おかゆ先輩の彼氏のつもりで、もう、うっ！ってやってしまいました。もう最高でした。ありがとうございました本当に。お返しします、すいません、ありがとうございました。
I'm really sorry to all the Onigiri (fans), but in that moment, I pretended to be Okayu-senpai's boyfriend and went "Ugh!" It was absolute bliss. Thank you so much! I'll return her now, sorry!
というね、エモエモな、カッコいいからエモいまでのパートがありましたけれど、楽しんでいただけてますか？
We had such an emotional section, running the gamut from cool to sentimental! Are you guys having fun?!
ちょっとコメント見てみようかな。あ、エモすぎた。泣いた。わかる、わかる、めっちゃエモいよね。ちはもなんかやりながら「エモすぎる、これ」と思って、やってましたよ。
Let's check out the comments. Oh, "It was too emotional, I cried." I get it! I totally get it, it really was emotional! I was performing while thinking, "This is way too emotional!"
ありがとう。めっちゃよかったよね。
Thank you. It was really amazing, wasn't it?
さあ、ということでね。ちょっとあの、ちは、あの、喋らせると、あの、喋りすぎてしまうので、ちょっと次のパートにいきたいんですが、ここからは嬉しいお知らせとなります！
All right! If you let me keep talking, I'll just talk forever, so I should move on to the next segment. From here on, it's time for some exciting announcements!
輪堂千速 誕生記念2026、グッズ販売の告知となります！生誕グッズが出るぞー！こちらをご覧ください、ドン！
I have announcements for the Rindo Chihaya Birthday Celebration 2026 merchandise sale! Birthday merch is coming! Take a look at this, bam!
はーい、盛りだくさんですね！イラストは、とりだもの先生に描いていただきました。ありがとうございます！ギターをね、弾いてるライブのワンシーンをイメージして描いていただきました。いや、めっちゃカッコいいよね！
Yes! There's a ton of stuff! The illustration was drawn by Toridamono-sensei. Thank you so much! It was drawn to look like a snapshot of me playing guitar live. It looks so cool, right?
それではね、詳細を見ていきましょう。まずは、こちら！
Now, let's look at the details. First up is this one!
えー、千速バースデーフェスTシャツ2026でございます！キービジュアルのイラスト全身を使用したカッコ可愛いTシャツです。バンドTシャツっぽくしたくてね、ちょっとロゴとかいかつい感じにしてもらったので、ぜひぜひライブ、ライブとか日常でも着てもらえたら嬉しいです！
Here is the "Chihaya BD Fes T-shirt 2026"! It's a cool and cute T-shirt featuring the full-body key visual illustration. I wanted to give it a band T-shirt vibe, so I had the logo designed to look a bit edgy. I'd love for you to wear it to lives or even just for everyday use!
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this one!
えー、ピックケースキーホルダーです。お気に入りのピックを入れて、おしゃれに持ち運べるキーホルダーです。キーホルダーがメインで、3枚のピックは付属品としてついています。ピックケースホルダーには、ピックが1枚入る仕様です。あの、今回のために書いたサインとかロゴとか、あとは「Flat Out」っていうロゴ、今回のね、タイトルにもなってる「Flat Out」のロゴが描かれてるピックがセットになっています。続いては、こちら！
Here is the "Pick Case Key Ring"! It's a key ring that lets you carry your favorite pick around in style. The key ring itself is the main item, and it comes with three picks as accessories. The pick case can hold one pick. The set includes picks featuring a specially hand-drawn signature, the logo, and the "Flatout" logo from our event title. Next up is this!
ちはとお出かけバッグです！前にポーチがついていて、前のポーチをひっくり返すと、中身を見せて推しバッグにチェンジできる、ちょっとね、機能性のあるバッグ、斜めがけのバッグになっています。いろんなところ、これでお出かけしてください！そして、続いては、こちら！
This is the "Outing with Chihaya Bag"! It has a front pouch, and if you turn that pouch inside out, it becomes a clear window to show off your merchandise as an "oshi bag"! It's a highly functional crossbody bag. I hope you'll take it with you on all your outings! And next up is this!
どこでもふぐたろうティッシュカバー！ふんわりとした質感の、ふぐたろうモチーフのティッシュカバーです。え、可愛いよね！お家でも車でも職場でも、ふぐたろうを連れて行けます。そして、続いては、こちら！
The "Everywhere Fugutaro Tissue Cover"! It's a soft-textured tissue cover designed with a Fugutaro motif. It's so cute, right? You can bring Fugutaro with you at home, in the car, or at the office! And next up is this!
シチュエーションボイスです。タイトルは「ライブリハーサルボイス」。ライブ前のリハーサルで、ドキドキ、緊張している千速のシチュエーションボイスになっておりますので、ドキドキの緊張感をね、ぜひ聞きに来てください。そして、フルセット購入特典もあります！こちら！
A "Situation Voice Pack"! The title is "Live Rehearsal Voice." It features Chihaya feeling super nervous and excited during rehearsals right before the live show. Please listen and experience that heart-pounding tension! We also have full set purchase bonuses! Here they are!
直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードです！全部ね、直筆で千速がサインを書きますのでね、ぜひぜひフルセットで購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです。そして特典ボイス、タイトルは「ライブ後、君と」になります。先ほどのね、ボイスと合わせて聞くと、またよりエモさを感じられるのではないかなと思うので、ぜひこちらも聞いてみてください。改めて、フルセットはこちらになります！
It's an instax-style bromide card featuring a hand-signed autograph and a foil-stamped printed message! I will be hand-signing every single one of these, so I would be absolutely thrilled if you got the full set! The bonus voice is titled "With You, After the Live." If you listen to it together with the rehearsal voice, it'll feel even more emotional, so please give it a listen! To recap, here is the full set!
やっぱね、これ全部、Tシャツ着て、バッグ持って、キーホルダーつけて、え、ふぐたろう持って、どこでも行ける千速セット、千速セットなので、ま、買うならフルセットの方が、いいよね？21時、この後21時カートオープンとなりますので、えーと、数量限定ではないのでぜひね、あの、ゆっくり購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです。よろしくお願いします！
After all, if you wear the T-shirt, carry the bag, attach the key ring, and hold Fugutaro, you'll have the complete "Chihaya Set" to go anywhere with me! So, if you're getting them, the full set is the best choice, right? The cart opens at 9:00 PM tonight! It's not limited in quantity, so feel free to take your time making your purchase. Thank you so much!
お願いします。
Please support me.
そして皆様待望の、お知らせがございます！
And I have an announcement you've all been waiting for!
こちら！
Here it is!
なんと！神堂千速ソロとして初めてのオリ曲
Incredible! Chihaya Rindo's very first original solo song,
「Flatout」がこのあと24時、7月9日木曜日の0時、このあとね、3時間ちょい後くらいからデジタルリリースされます！
"Flatout," will be digitally released at midnight tonight, July 9th (Thu)! That's in a little over three hours!
やったー！
Yay!
このポーズしてる。今回のライブのタイトルにもなっている「Flatout」はオリ曲のタイトルでございました！
I'm doing this pose. "Flatout," which is also the title of today's concert, is the title of my original song!
えー、この配信が終わったあとに、MVが公開されますので、そちらもぜひお楽しみに！
The music video will be released after this stream, so please look forward to that as well!
概要欄にね、あの、のちのち多分リンクが貼られたり貼られなかったりすると思うのでそちらもチェックしてみてください。
I'll probably put a link in the description later, so please check that out.
え、新曲、このあとやっぱ早速聴きたいですよね？
Now, you want to hear the new song right away, don't you?
このあと披露するので絶対に聴いてください。
I'll perform it later, so please make sure to stay and listen.
最後まで、最後までね、チャンネルはそのままで見ていってくださいね。
Watch until the very end, and please don't change the channel.
以上、神堂千速生誕祭2026のグッズ情報と、リリース情報でした！
That's all for the Chihaya Rindo Birthday Festival 2026 merchandise and release info!
みんな買ってね、サブスクでも聴いてね！
Please buy the goods, and listen on streaming platforms!
はい！
Yes!
ということで、怒涛のお知らせコーナーでした。ここからいよいよライブもクライマックスです。でもまだまだあります！
So that was a whirlwind announcement segment. The live concert is reaching its climax now, but we still have more!
盛り上がる準備できてますか？最後一緒にぶち上げていこうね！
Are you ready to get hyped? Let's blow the roof off together for the finale!
では、準備してきます。
Well, I'll go get ready.
あ、そのチャンネルはそのままで。
Ah, keep the channel as it is.
ワタリドリ
[Song: Wataridori]
I wanna fly so high / Yeah, I know my wings are dried
「翼仰げば」って人は云う
"Look at birds' wings," I've heard people say
さの向こうにあるは無情
Far beyond that, lies heartlessness
飛べる者 落ちる者
Those that had flown, those that had fallen
誰も見てない 気にも留めない それでも飛び続けた
No one is watching, not even noticing, still, I've continued to fly
傷ついた言葉乗せ 運びたいから
If you've been hurt, put it into words, because I'll carry you
追いかけて届くよう
Let's pursue and reach
僕等 一心に羽ばたいて
Fervently, we'll flap our wings
問いかけて嘆いた夜
Ask a question to the grieving night
故郷は一層輝いて
More than ever, my hometown shines
ワタリドリの様に今
Right now, like migrating birds,
旅に立つよ
I'll depart on a journey
ありもしないストーリーを
And draw for you a story
描いてみせるよ
That doesn't exist
I wanna fly so far / Away with my guitar
「一人じゃない」って人々は歌う
"I'm not alone," I've heard men and women sing
間違いじゃない 理想論でもない
It's not a mistake, not even an idealistic thought
ただ頼って生きたくはない
I just don't want to live like this anymore
誰も聴いていない 気にも留めない それでも歌い続けた
No one is listening, not even stopping me, still, I continue to sing
傷ついたあなたを 笑わせたいから
Because I want to make you, who has been wounded, smile
追い風 届けるよ
I'll deliver a tailwind to you
僕等 一心に羽ばたいて
Fervently, we'll flap our wings
遠い過去を背負ってた
You, burdened with a distant past
あなたを未来へ運ぶよ
I'll carry you to the future
ワタリドリの様に今
Right now, like migrating birds,
群れをなして
We flock together
大それた四重奏を
Until the day an outrageous quartet
奏で終える日まで
Finishes playing
All this time we come and we grow / And now it's time that we should go
But we both know that this is for sure / It's not the end of the world / We'll see you one day
追いかけて届くよう
Let's pursue and reach
僕等 一心に羽ばたいて
Fervently, we'll flap our wings
問いかけて嘆いた夜
Ask a question to the grieving night
朝焼け色に染まっていく
We'll go steeped in the colors of the sunrise
ワタリドリの様にいつか
Like a migrating bird,
舞い戻るよ
Come back one day
ありもしないストーリーを
A story that doesn't exist
いつかまた会う日まで
Until we meet again
はい！ということで、輪堂千速生誕祭、ここまで見てくれたみんな本当にありがとうございます！
Yes! And with that, everyone who has watched Chihaya Rindo's Birthday Festival up to this point, thank you so much!
えー、次が本当にラストの曲です。
Next up is truly the last song.
えー、この曲は、いつかみんなと、現地で会って、ライブができたときに、最後に歌えたらいいなって、
I had this song made with the hope that one day, when we can meet in person and have a concert,
そんな想いで、千速のいろんな気持ちを込めて作ってもらった曲です。
we can sing this at the end, pouring all of Chihaya's feelings into it.
千速の、初めてのオリ曲、聴いてください。Flat out。
Please listen to Chihaya's first original song, "Flat out".
メランコリーのリフレイン 午前３時
A melancholy refrain at 3:00 AM
夢を見るには少し 遅すぎた Midnight
It's a bit too late to be dreaming, midnight
言葉にならないままの想いが
Before these wordless feelings...
溢れだしてしまう前に 飛びだした部屋 光を見たくて
...begin to overflow, I ran out of my room, wanting to see the light
“どうせ”だって 何度だって 諦めようとしたって
Even if I tried to give up time and time again, saying "what's the point"
“だけど” “きっと” 今日もそっと 伸ばした手 あの星まで
But still, surely, today I gently reach my hand out again to that star
自分さえだませない 嘘はもうやめて
Stop the lies that can't even fool yourself
踏み込め
Step on it!
駆け抜けて 音も風も抜き去って
Dash through, overtaking both sound and wind
迷いさえも振り切って スピードを上げて
Shake off even my doubts and speed up
行かなくちゃ 夜のまだ その向こうへ
I have to go, further beyond the night
見たこともない世界へ 今 最高速度で
To a world I've never seen before, now at maximum speed
高鳴る方へ
Towards where my heart beats fast
答えなんてなくたって ただこうして いたいだけ
Even if there's no answer, I just want to be like this
未完成で不完全な道の先まで 行ける、信じて
I can go to the end of this unfinished, imperfect road, believe me
差し障りないように生きた日々
The days lived just to avoid causing trouble
諦めの言い訳を探すのをやめて
Stop looking for excuses to give up
もどかしい気持ち 窓の向こうに
My frustrating feelings, beyond the window
輝くあの星みたいに ああ なりたかったんだ
Ah, I wanted to be like that shining star
足りない物だらけだって どれだけ離されたって
Even if I'm full of flaws, no matter how far behind I'm left
止まればそこまでなんだ
If I stop, that's where it ends
進め 進め 未来を変える瞬間は いつかじゃなくて今なんだ
Move forward, move forward! The moment to change the future isn't "someday", it's right now!
進め 進め 先へ さあ
Move forward, move forward, further ahead, come on!
もっと遠くまで
Even further away!
確かめに行くんだ Flat out
I'm going to make sure, flat out!
駆け抜けて 夢に見たその舞台へ
Dash through to that stage I saw in my dreams
決して振り返らないで スピードを上げて
Never look back, speed up
行かなくちゃ 夜のまだ その向こうへ
I have to go, further beyond the night
見たこともない世界へ 今 最高速度で
To a world I've never seen before, now at maximum speed
信じる方へ
Towards what I believe in
答えなんてなくたって ただこうして走り出したんだ
Even if there's no answer, I've just started running like this
止まらないよ
I won't stop!
さあ あの星に届け
Come on, reach that star!
輪堂千速生誕祭2026、見ていただいて本当にありがとうございました！
Whew, thank you all so much for watching Chihaya Rindo's Birthday Festival 2026!
これからも、みんなと向こうの景色たくさん見に行きたいです。
From here on out, I want to go see many more sights beyond with all of you.
これからも千速のことを好きでいて、ついてきてくれたら嬉しいです。
I'd be so happy if you keep loving Chihaya and follow along with me.
本当に今日はありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much for today!
ありがとうねー！
Thank you!
輪堂千速生誕LIVEにお越しいただきありがとうございます 初めてのライブはどうでしたか？？
[On-Screen Message] Thank you for coming to Chihaya Rindo's Birthday Live. How was my first concert??
見てくれたキミがいて初めてこの空が完成します
[On-Screen Message] This sky is only complete because you were here to watch it.
いつかキミの声が直接きけるその時まで これからも走り続けるよ！！！ 今日は本当にありがとう
[On-Screen Message] Until the day I can hear your voice in person, I'll keep running forward!!! Thank you so much for today!
輪堂千幸生誕LIVE
Chihaya Rindo Birthday LIVE
お越しいただきありがとうございます
Thank you so much for coming!
初めてのライブはどうでしたか？？
How did you like my very first live show??
見にくれたキミ達で初めて『輪』完成します
With all of you here to watch, our circle is finally complete.
いつかキミの声が直接きけるその時まで
Until the day I can finally hear your voices directly...
これからも走り続けるよ！！！
I will keep running forward!!!
今日は本当にありがとう
Thank you so much for today!